readytobuy.it 2015-09-17

# 

  **ReadyToBuy.it Site (websites and mobile sites) Privacy Policy**

**ReadyToBuy.it may be referred to herein as "READYTOBUY.IT”, "WE", OR "US", whether in uppercase, lowercase, or a combination.**

By continuing to access and/or use any READYTOBUY.IT Site service following any update to this Privacy Policy, you are indicating and deemed to have agreed that that you have read, understand, and agree to its updates and modifications and the entirety of the updated Privacy Policy.

Thank You for accessing or having accessed any of READYTOBUY.IT ’s Sites or services, by way of the internet web sites, mobile device, smart-phone, tablet, reader, application or app, social media (such as Facebook and Twitter), a video service (such as YouTube or Vimeo) (none of which READYTOBUY.IT is affiliated with), or any other device or method now known or developed in the future (individually and collectively, “the,” “any,” or “a” “READYTOBUY.IT Platform” or “READYTOBUY.IT Site” or “READYTOBUY.IT service” (all sometimes collectively referred to as, “Platform). This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout every READYTOBUY.IT Site, Platform and service governing the use of personally identifiable information about users of our various Platforms and users of services available on or through each READYTOBUY.IT Platform (the "services"). 

**PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**

READYTOBUY.IT may make changes to the Privacy Policy, any READYTOBUY.IT Platform, content, or services at any time. The latest Privacy Policy will be posted or be available through http://www.readytobuy.it/privacy.html, and You agree that You should and will always review it prior to using any READYTOBUY.IT Site or services.

Because of the rapidly evolving nature of the internet, computers, mobile technologies, and other technologies, in our attempts to make our user experience better, and for other aesthetic and business reasons, READYTOBUY.IT may change, update and modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. READYTOBUY.IT will post its updated Privacy Policy at http://www.readytobuy.it/privacy.html so You may always be aware of what has changed. If any modification is unacceptable to You, You shall cease using the READYTOBUY.IT Platform (i.e., Site, and service) right away. If You do not cease using the (each and every) READYTOBUY.IT Platform (i.e., Site, and service) right away, You will be conclusively   deemed to have accepted the change(s). Except as stated elsewhere, any amended Privacy Policy shall automatically be effective as soon as it is initially posted, except if READYTOBUY.IT states that it is giving advance notice of any amended term to be effective on a date in the future. Please check the Privacy Policy and any guidelines periodically for changes. Except as posted by READYTOBUY.IT to the http://www.readytobuy.it/privacy.html, this Privacy Policy may not be otherwise amended, and no term may be waived by READYTOBUY.IT , except in a writing, hand signed by pen on paper (or as set forth below) by You and an authorized representative of READYTOBUY.IT . For purposes of this provision, a "writing" does not include an email message, text, chat, or the like, sent from any device existing now or later developed and a signature does not include an electronic signature.

This READYTOBUY.IT Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of READYTOBUY.IT ’s policies and practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information through any (each and every) READYTOBUY.IT Platform (i.e., Site, and service). We define Personal Information as information that allows someone to identify or contact you, including for example your name, address, telephone number, and email address.

By registering with us or accessing or using any READYTOBUY.IT Platform (i.e., Site, and service), you expressly consent to the information handling practices in this Privacy Policy. If you reside outside the United States, you understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing personal information may be less stringent than in your country.

This Privacy Policy is a part of our Website http://www.readytobuy.it/terms.html. If any term of this Privacy Policy is inconsistent or conflicts with any term of the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy will control. Capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy but not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given to them in the Terms of Use.

**Personal Information You Provide to us**

When you register to use any READYTOBUY.IT Platform (i.e., Site, and service), we may collect your name, e-mail address and e-mail preferences, and password for your account. We may also ask you to provide additional information on an optional basis in connection with setting up your account. You may also register by using your log-in credentials from social networking websites, including Facebook, Twitter, or LinkedIn. When you register in this way, we may collect Personal Information from the social networking websites that you have given us permission to collect or made publicly available. The information READYTOBUY.IT obtains may depend on your privacy settings with the social networking website. When you purchase any materials, services, from READYTOBUY.IT , we may collect your name, phone number, e-mail address, mailing address, billing address, complete credit card information that enables us to receive your payment (however we do not retain your credit card number unless requested) and federal tax identification number or European Union VAT number as applicable. When you give us feedback, we may collect any information that is contained in your feedback. When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, fax, or letter, we collect your e-mail address, fax number, or mailing address, and any information contained in the e-mail, fax, or letter you send us.

**Personal Information Collected via Technology**

As you use any READYTOBUY.IT Platform (i.e., Site, and service), some information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, access time, mobile phone model, and telecom carrier. We may also store a small text file called a "Cookie" on your computer or phone to store certain information about your use of any READYTOBUY.IT Platform. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer or phone until you delete them). We may collect and store information locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage and application data caches. We may collect details of how you used any READYTOBUY.IT Platform. We may share certain information with Google Analytics, for example. (Google's privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy).

**Use of Information**

We use your Personal Information to provide the READYTOBUY.IT Site, and services to you, to respond to requests that you make, to personalize your experience on and using any READYTOBUY.IT Platform, to improve any (each and every) READYTOBUY.IT Platform, and to better tailor the features, performance, and support of each READYTOBUY.IT Platform .

We may use your Personal Information to send you electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, unless you have requested not to receive such promotional communications from us. We may also use your Personal Information to send you READYTOBUY.IT services-related communications, and you may opt out of these communications if you terminate your account.

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information at our discretion. "Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information.

Any feedback you provide will be governed by the Terms of Use.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

We may provide your Personal Information to specified third parties for sending you promotional e-mails relating to such third parties' products, unless you have requested us not to receive promotional communications from such third parties.

We may provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide any READYTOBUY.IT Platform However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information (except pursuant to a legal requirement such as a subpoena or warrant).

We may provide your credit card and related billing and payment information to third party service providers engaged on READYTOBUY.IT 's behalf, including payment processors and/or credit agencies, for the purposes of checking credit, effecting payment, and servicing your accounts.

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our Affiliates in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

We will not share any Personal Information with any of our app developer partners.

Information that we collect from you, including PII, is considered a business asset. Accordingly, if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, or if we are acquired, e.g., as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition, or asset sale, your PII may be disclosed or transferred to the third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction.

**Law Enforcement Compliance**

We may be required by law, or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of law, to record some or all of your communications on or through any READYTOBUY.IT Platform. We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information (including your account information) and your communications with us including through any (each and every) READYTOBUY.IT Platform , if required by law or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of law, or if we believe in our sole and unfettered discretion that disclosure is necessary to: (1) satisfy or comply with relevant laws, regulation or legal process; (2) respond to lawful requests, or to respond to subpoenas or warrants or court orders served on us; or (3) to protect and defend ours, our Affiliates,' other users,' or your, rights, property or safety; and (4) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

**Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information**

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you may have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive.

Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you administrative e-mails regarding any READYTOBUY.IT Platform , including, for example, purchase confirmation, account creation confirmation, and notices of material changes to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

You may change your email address and password for the service by editing it in your account page. You may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request, only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

**Regarding Children**

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about Users who are under the age of 13. READYTOBUY.IT recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. No READYTOBUY.IT Platform is intended for children **under the age of 13**. READYTOBUY.IT does not target its services or Platforms to children under 13. READYTOBUY.IT does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS ANY READYTOBUY.IT PLATFORM AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. IF READYTOBUY.IT LEARNS THAT PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF PERSONS LESS THAN 13 YEARS OF AGE HAS BEEN COLLECTED ON OR THROUGH A READYTOBUY.IT PLATFORM, READYTOBUY.IT WILL TAKE THE APPROPRIATE STEPS TO DELETE THIS INFORMATION.

IF YOU ARE THE PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN OF A CHILD THE AGE OF 13 WHO HAS BECOME A READYTOBUY.IT PLATFORM USER, THEN PLEASE CONTACT READYTOBUY.IT AT Privacy@READYTOBUY.IT TO HAVE THAT CHILD'S ACCOUNT TERMINATED AND INFORMATION DELETED.

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your children’s access to certain types of material on the internet. While READYTOBUY.IT does not endorse these sites, services, or products, and disclaims any responsibility in connection with them, we provide information about them as a public service.

  1. [OnGuard Online](http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking.html), maintained by the Federal Trade Commission.
  2. [WiredSafety](http://www.wiredsafety.org/)
  3. [Netsmartz.org](http://netsmartz.org/)
  4. [The Child Safety Network](http://www.csn.org/index.jsp)
  5. [Control Kids](http://www.controlkids.com/)
  6. [CyberSitter](http://www.solidoak.com/)
  7. [NetNanny](http://www.netnanny.com/)

**Third Party Sites, Third Party services, and Third Party Materials**

Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to Third Party Sites, Third Party services or Third Party Materials that have links or are provided through any READYTOBUY.IT Platform. Third party providers of such Third Party Sites, Third Party services or Third Party Materials, may collect (via tracking technologies like Cookies or web beacons) and use Anonymous Information regarding your interaction with the Third Party Sites, Third Party services or Third Party Materials that they deliver and with which you interact.

**NOTICE TO EUROPEAN USERS**

**The information You enter on or through a READYTOBUY.IT Platform or otherwise provide to READYTOBUY.IT may be transferred outside of the European Union to the United States of America, which does not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European Union. In particular, You are advised that the United States of America uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation, and self-regulation. Article 26 of the European Union's Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC, 1995 O.J. (L 281) 31) allows for transfer of personal data from the European Union to a third country if the individual has unambiguously given his consent to the transfer of personal information, regardless of the third country's level of protection. By agreeing to the Terms and this Privacy Policy, You consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States of America, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European Union and to the processing of that information by READYTOBUY.IT on its servers located in the United States of America as described in this Privacy Policy.**

**Security**

We make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal information, but no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks connected to handling information on the internet.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

This Privacy Policy may be amended at any time in accordance with the section titled "Updates" herein and in the http://www.readytobuy.it/terms.html.
